Inventory of the G. Walter Mapp Papers 1895-1935
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Correspondence of G. Walter Mapp, 1895-1935. (Box 1-8)
  - General Correspondence, 1895-1935. (Box 1-7)
    - General Correspondence: Fo-J, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 3:1-276)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Thomas L. Johnson, Hampton, Virginia, 1911., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:246)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Thomas L. Johnson, Hampton, Virginia, 1928., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:247)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. C. Johnson, Suffolk, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:248)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Judge William F. Johnson, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1931-1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:249)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. L. Johnson, Craddockville, Virginia, [1911]., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:250)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Charles A. Johnston, Bluefield, West Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:251)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Alice Johnstone, Danville, Kentucky, 1906, 1911., 13 items. (Box-folder 3:252)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. G. Jones, Lexington, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:253)
      - Correspondence from A. H. Jones, Painter, Virginia, 1910., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:254)
      - Correspondence from C. E. Jones, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:255)
      - Correspondence from E. Clarence Jones and Company, New York, New York, 1906., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:256)
      - Correspondence from F. E. Jones, Stockton, Maryland, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:257)
      - Correspondence from George E. Jones, Quinby, Virginia, 1906-1911., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:258)
      - Correspondence from H. Stewart Jones, Keller and Richmond, Virginia, 1910, 1931., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:259)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Hugh W. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:260)
      - Correspondence from J. Paul Jones, Lynchburg, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:261)
      - Duplicate correspondence to James P. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 1926., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:262)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Jeter Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:263)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mrs. Kate Nelson Jones, Greenbackville, Virginia, 1914., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:264)
      - Correspondence from Margaret S. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:265)
      - Correspondence from Margaret V. Jones, Richmond, Virginia, 1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:266)
      - Correspondence from S. R. Jones, Belle Haven, Virginia, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:267)
      - Correspondence from Congressman William A. Jones, Washington, D.C., 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:268)
      - Correspondence from W. R. Jones, Chicago, Illinios, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:269)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Harry Jordan, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:270)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. P. M. Joyce, Norfolk, Virginia, 1922., 3 items. (Box-folder 3:271)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with G. G. Jeynes, Onancock, Virginia, 1912., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:272)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with T. A. Joynes, Baltimore, Maryland, 1929., 4 items. (Box-folder 3:273A)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lt. Commander W. W. Joynes, Norfolk, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:273B)
      - Correspondence from Adelaide Justice, Jenkins Bridge, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 3:274)
      - Correspondence from Alexander Justis, Wattsville, Virginia, 1909., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:275)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Asher L. Justis, Leemant, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 3:276)
    - General Correspondence: K-M, 1895-1935., Note: "Duplicate correspondence" refers to unsigned copies of letters by Mapp. "Original correspondence" refers to signed letters written to Mapp. (Box-folder 4:1-285)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Kappa Alpha Order, Alpha Zeta Chapter, Williamsburg, Virginia., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:1)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. R. Keas, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:2)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Charles R. Kelley, Richmond, Virginia, 1918-1926., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:3)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Editor Kister, Strasburg, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:4)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lucien Keith, Warrington, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:5)
      - Correspondence with Mr. Kellan, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:6)
      - Duplicate correspondence to E. L. Kellan, Painter, Virginia, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:7)
      - Duplicate correspondence to F. C. Kellam, Richmond, Virginia, 1914., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:8)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. S. Kellan, Belle Haven, Virginia, 1911-1930., 6 items. (Box-folder 4:9)
      - Correspondence from the Reverend T. Kellan, Louisville, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:10)
      - Correspondence from V. H. Kellan, Norfolk, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:11)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Walter W. Keller, Roanoke, Virginia, 1927., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:12)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Mrs. J. C. (Mabel P.) Kelley, 1914., 7 items. (Box-folder 4:13)
      - Correspondence from S. L. Kelley, Richmond, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:14)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Kellogg and Dickinson, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:15)
      - Duplicate correspondence to C. W. Kells, Gates City, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:16)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Kelly and Nicholaides, Washington, D.C., 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:17)
      - Duplicate correspondence to B. P. Kelly, Exmore, Virginia, 1932-1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:18)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Claude W. Kelly, Pocomoke City, Maryland, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:19)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. E. Kelly, New Church, Virginia, 1923., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:20)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Margaret Kelly, Westchester, Pennsylvania, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:21)
      - Correspondence from D. Arthur Kelsey, Norfolk, Virginia, 1906, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:22)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Fletcher Kemp, Rosslyn, Virginia, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:23)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with William G. Kerbin, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1911-1924., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:24)
      - Correspondence from Lana A. Kern, Winchester, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:25)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. W. Kerns, Bloxom, Virginia, 1927, 1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:26)
      - Duplicate correspondence to George F. Kesler, Skipwith, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:27)
      - Correspondence from Mr. And Mrs. James Kibler, Chase City, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:28)
      - Correspondence from E. C. Killam, Locustville, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:29)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Asher Killman, Parksley, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:30)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Charles Killmon, Locustville, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:31)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Noble Killmon, Daughterty, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:32)
      - Duplicate correspondence to T. O. Killmon, Painter, Virginia, 1927., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:33)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. B. Kimmerly, Old Point, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:34)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Clayton P. King, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:35)
      - Correspondence from J. D. King, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:36)
      - Correspondence from William F. King, Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:37)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with H. H. Kirkman, Roanoke, Virginia, 1928., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:38)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Frank Kitts, North Tazewell, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:39)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. F. Knox, Baltimore, Maryland, 1918, 1922., 14 items. (Box-folder 4:40)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Charles E. Kofflin, Royal Oak, Michigan, 1918, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:41)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George W. Koiner, Richmond, Virginia, 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:42)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Labor Herald, Richmond, Virginia, 1926., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:43)
      - Duplicate correspondence to "Lady Esther," Chicago, Illinois, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:44)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. S. Lamberth, State Senator from Bedford City, Virginia, 1925-1926., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:45)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George W. "Eizy" Land, Princess Anne, Virginia, 1911., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:46)
      - Correspondence from Franklin K. Lane, Washington, D.C., 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:47)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with G. E. T. Lane, Port Haywood, Virginia, 1924, 1928-1929., 11 items. (Box-folder 4:48)
      - Correspondence from Edward Lang, Silva, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:49)
      - Correspondence from James C. Lang, Temperanceville, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:50)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. H. Long, Accomac, Virginia, 1925-1926., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:51)
      - Correspondence from Ed Langley, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:52)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Charles M. Lankford, Franktown, Virginia, 1911, 1931, 1933., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:53)
      - Correspondence from F. G. Lankford, Morattico, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:54)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. Frank Lankford, Mears, Virginia, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:55)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Charles T. Lassiter, Petersburg, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:56)
      - Correspondence from A. D. Latane, Tappahannock, Virginia, 1918., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:57)
      - Duplicate correspondence to James Laughton, Norfolk, Virginia, [1911]., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:58)
      - Correspondence from A. R. Lawrence, Richmond, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:59)
      - Correspondence from W. F. Lawson, Jeffs, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:60)
      - Duplicate correspondence to J. R. Lay, Coeburg, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:61)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with George W. Layman, Newport News, Virginia, 1926-1929., 11 items. (Box-folder 4:62)
      - Correspondence from P. A. Layne, Cullen, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:63)
      - Correspondence from I. L. Layton, Catlett, Virginia, 1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:64)
      - Telegram from O. L. Layton, Newport News, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:65)
      - Correspondence from J. C. W. Leatherbury, Onancock, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:66)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Annie Lecato, Keller, Virginia, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:67)
      - Correspondence from George Lecato, Cleveland, Ohio, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:68)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Lee Lecato, Accomac, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:69)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Riley U. LeCato, Onancock, Virginia, 1911, 1927, 1935., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:70)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Susie LeCato, Belle Haven, Virginia, 1922-1934., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:71)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Virginia F. LeCato, Portsmouth, Virginia, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:72)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with William N. LeCato, New York, New York, 1911-1928., 16 items. (Box-folder 4:73)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. H. Lechty, Richmond, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:74)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Robert Lecky, Bon Air, Virginia, 1922., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:75)
      - Correspondence from L. Ledman, Manassas, Virginia, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:76)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with William McDonald Lee, Richmond, Virginia, 1918-1924., 8 items. (Box-folder 4:77)
      - Correspondence from George W. Leggett, London Bridge, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:78)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with G. Franklin Lenz, Newport News, Virginia, 1931., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:79)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Dr. Southgate Leigh, Norfolk, Virginia, 1904, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:80)
      - Correspondence from Moe levy, Newport News, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:81)
      - Correspondence from Edna B. Lewis, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:82)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Franklin C. Lewis, Hopkins, Virginia, 1924, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:83)
      - Correspondence from J. M. Lewis, Gloucester, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:84)
      - Duplicate correspondence to James M. Lewis, Tappahannock, Virginia, 1924., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:85)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with John T. Lewis, Hallwood, Virginia, 1911-1922., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:86)
      - Duplicate correspondence to M. J. Lewis, Pocomoke City, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:87)
      - Correspondence from Maryan B. Lewis, Culpeper, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:88)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Obed Lewis, Nassawadox, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:89)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. T. J. Lane, Hopkins, Virginia, 1931, 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:90)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. H. Lichty, Richmond, Virginia, 1931-1934., 8 items. (Box-folder 4:91)
      - Correspondence from William Minor Lile, Charlottesville, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:92)
      - Correspondence from A. J. Lilliston, Accomack, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:93)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. J. Lilliston, Parksley, Virginia, 1924, 1929., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:94)
      - Correspondence from Steve Lindsey, Danville, Virginia, ca. 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:95)
      - Correspondence from A. W. Linthicum, Churchland, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:96)
      - Correspondence from Aron Linton, Saxis, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:97)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Herman E. Linton, Washington, D.C., 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:98)
      - Correspondence from W. P. Lipscomb, Suffolk, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:99)
      - Correspondence from Henry E. Litchford, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:100)
      - Correspondence from The Literary Digest, New York, New York, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:101)
      - Correspondence from H. L. Littel, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:102)
      - Duplicate correspondence to H. A. Littleton, Parksley, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:103)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mrs. Hattie Livingstone, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:104)
      - Telegram from M. Ljungstedt, Bethesda, Maryland, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:105)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Helen Lockie, Portsmouth, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:106)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Lowe's State Theater, Norfolk, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:107)
      - Correspondence from F. S. Loitten, Tazewell, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:108)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with R. J. Long, Portsmouth, Virginia, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:109)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Henry T. Louthan, Staunton, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:110)
      - Correspondence of Thomas B. Love, Dallas, Texas, 1928., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:111)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Otto Lowe, Cape Charles, Virginia, 1933-1934., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:112)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with D. R. Luttrell, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:113)
      - Duplicate correspondence to R. E. Luttrell, 1929., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:114)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with David Allen Lyon, Jr., Petersburg, Virginia, 1929., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:115)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Sallie P. Mable, East Orange, New York, 1932., 6 items. (Box-folder 4:116)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Willie Madre, Camp 25, Harrington, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:117)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. P. Magee, Newport News, Virginia, 1931., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:118)
      - Correspondence from J. S. Malbon, Norfolk, Virginia, 1912., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:119)
      - Correspondence from Herbert C. Mallory, Camp Custer, Michigan, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:120)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Edwin M. Mann, Kenbridge, Virginia, 1922., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:121)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with G. C. Mann, Montross, Virginia, 1918., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:122)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Richard H. Mann, Petersburg, Virginia, 1921., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:123)
      - Correspondence from William Hodges Mann, Petersburg, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:124)
      - Correspondence from J. L. Manson, Blackstone, Virginia, 1925., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:125)
      - Duplicate correspondence to the Mantle Lamp Company, Chicago, Illinois, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:126)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Charles G. Maphis, University, Virginia, 1922, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:127)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Maplewood Inn, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1931., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:128)
      - Duplicate correspondence from G. Walter Mapp to Mapp's Campaign Headquarters, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 7 items. (Box-folder 4:129)
      - Correspondence from Ada [Mapp?], n.d., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:130)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Alf J. Mapp, Portsmouth, Virginia, 1928., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:131)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with C. W. Mapp, Richmond, Virginia, 1932., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:132)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with E. W. Mapp, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1932., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:133)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence between Mapp, Mildred (his wife), and his children, 1925, 1932., 10 items. (Box-folder 4:134)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. Brooks Mapp, 1911-1925., 19 items. (Box-folder 4:135)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. Brooks Mapp, 1927, 1935., 19 items. (Box-folder 4:136)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. E. Mapp (his father), Keller, Virginia, 1918-1920., 6 items. (Box-folder 4:137)
      - Correspondence from J. T. Mapp, Wachapreague, Virginia, 1923., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:138)
      - Correspondence from N. O. Mapp, Belle Haven, Virginia, 1911., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:139)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with R. H. Mapp, Cape Henry, Virginia, 1911, 1927., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:140)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. E. Marchant, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:141)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Rev. R. T. Marsh, Richmond, Virginia, 1928-1929., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:142)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Anniek Marshall, Chincoteague, Virginia. and Baltimore, Maryland, 1929, 1932., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:143)
      - Correspondence from Chester Marshall, Oyster Bay, New York, 1935., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:144)
      - Correspondence from R. L. Marshall, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1911., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:145)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Robert T. Marshall, Hampton Roads, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:146)
      - Duplicate correspondence to S. W. Marshall, Mears, Virginia, 1934., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:147)
      - Duplicate correspondence to T. S. Marshall, Roanoke, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:148)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Webster Marshall, Hallwood, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:149)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Alvah H. Martin, Jr., Norfolk, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:150)
      - Correspondence from H. J. Martin, Craddockville, Virginia, 1906., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:151)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. K. Martin, Harborton, Virginia, 1912., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:152)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. S. Martin, Pungoteague, Virginia, 1922, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:153)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Thomas S. Martin, U. S. Senate, Washington, D.C., 1911., 6 items. (Box-folder 4:154)
      - Duplicate correspondence to W. G. Martin, Roanoke, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:155)
      - Correspondence from Jessie Marvin, Wytheville, Virginia, 1902., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:156)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. J. Mason, Bowman's Folly, Virginia, 1932., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:157)
      - Correspondence from A. M. Mason, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:158)
      - Duplicate correspondence to A. T. Mason, Harborton, Virginia, 1934., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:159)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Elizabeth L. Mason, Chincoteague, Virginia., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:160)
      - Correspondence from G. B. Mason, Pungoteague, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:161)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Hattie Mason, Snow Hill, Maryland, 1933., 2 items. (Box-folder 4:162)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Lorenzo D. Mason, Jr., Pocomoke City, Maryland, 1932., 6 items. (Box-folder 4:163)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with Lucy R. Mason, Richmond, Virginia, 1922., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:164)
      - Correspondence from O. F. Mason, Bloxom, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:165)
      - Duplicate correspondence to S. J. Mason, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1920., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:166)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. M. Mason, Ocean City, Maryland, 1922., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:167)
      - Correspondence from Thurman D. Mason, Camp Lee, Virginia., 3 items. (Box-folder 4:168)
      - Correspondence from W. N. Mason, Parksley, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:169)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Mathews Journal, Mathews Court House, Virginia, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:170)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with J. S. Mathias, Greenbush, Virginia, 1911-1927., 5 items. (Box-folder 4:171)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with A. C. Matthews, Temperanceville, Virginia, 1909-1933., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:172)
      - Duplicate correspondence to Martha S. Matthews, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:173)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with S. Wilins Matthews, Oak Hall, Virginia, 5 items. (Box-folder 4:174)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with W. J. Matthews, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1911-1932., 9 items. (Box-folder 4:175)
      - Correspondence from E. C. [Mautens?], Pensinsula Drug Co., Temperanceville, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:176)
      - Correspondence from Margaret Maxon, Danville, Virginia, 1922., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:177)
      - Correspondence from Douglas W. Maynard, Richmond, Virginia, 1929., 1 item. (Box-folder 4:178)
      - Duplicate and original correspondence with D. J. Mays, Richmond, Virginia, 1934., 4 items. (Box-folder 4:179)